# **ALEXANDER KOZLOV**

### Resume





### PERSONAL DATA

ADRESS: Russia. Crimea. Simferopol (Open for remote job / ready to

move)

EMAIL: itrefak@gmail.com

PHONE: +7 978 848 04 11

GITHUB: thohoh
TWITTER: @trefa
SKYPE: itrefa

### EDUCATION

SEPT 2013 - JUNE 2014 | SPECIALIST IN AUTOMATED MANAGEMENT OF TECHNOLOGICAL

PROCESSES.

Kherson National Technical University.

SEPT 2010 - JUNE 2013 BACHELOR IN AUTOMATED MANAGEMENT OF TECHNOLOGICAL

PROCESSES.

Kherson National Technical University.

## **ABOUT ME**

#### **SUMMARY**

Strong knowledge of Javascript. Understand principles and technics required to create a quality software. Familiar with data structures and sorting algorithms. I'm trying to write a maintainable, modular and testable code, also practicing TDD approach in my projects where appropriate. Constantly evolve, learn by doing.

The list of technologies I worked with will be further. Here is a link to my bookshelf. My favorite ones are "Code Complete" and "Clean Coder".

## EXPERIENCE

MAY 2014 - JAN 2016

FREELANCE / REMOTE / PART TIME

SPA, PSD to HTML, interfaces with complex logic, some node.js backend

JAN 2016 - APR 2016

HAPPY-GIRAFFE.RU

Front-end developer

# **COMPUTER SKILLS**

#### PROFICIENT IN

Javascript, HTML (Pug/Jade), CSS (Precompilers: Sass, Less)

**UNIT-TESTS** 

Jasmine, Mocha

FRAMEWORKS / LIBRARIES

AngularJS, KnockoutJS, jQuery, ExpressJS, Bootstrap

DEPENDENCY MANAGEMENT

Browserify, RequireJS/AMD

**DBMS** 

MongoDB

**Tools** 

git, Gulp, Grunt, Photoshop

## LANGUAGES

ENGLISH C1

RUSSIAN Native